Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/lalit-jangid-a20210147 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Skilled Multi-tasker Process Automation Banking

Lalit Jangid

Consultant at Quinnox Consultancy Services

Thane, Maharashtra, India

Summary

B.com(A&F), M.com(A&F), MBA -Finance with 3.5+ years of experience in FP&A, Reconciliation, Fund Administration, Experience in Business Valuation (Startup), Fund Accounting & Settlement good communicator with great interpersonal and team handling skills actively seeking for a Finance role to gain knowledge and hone my financial and management skills benefitting organizational & personal growth.

Experience

QUINNOX CONSULTANCY SERVICES LIMITED

Consultant

December 2022 - Present (1 year 8 months)

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Analyze, generate & conduct 30+ financial reports on daily/weekly/month end accounting activities

Streamlined reporting requirements by making report specific changes Perform daily Journal reconciliation, recon with the Bank TM1 system to reconcile MIS Reports

Completes task from refreshing the server for updating the data Generates reports & manages treasury to ensure compliance with GDPR is done

Updates various Bank reports Summary P&L, Comparative Statements, ALCO reports, administrative files, Hedging files, Wholesale files, Tax Workings File, Balance Sheet analysis

Updates data across various TM1 linked files and to reconcile them to match without any checks in TAT

Continuous support to reduce the overall TAT for files by streamlining the process

Asset Vantage Account Executive November 2021 - June 2022 (8 months)

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Learning and exploring different type of data feed on bankable assets (equities, mutual funds, bonds, hedge funds, etc.), identify the sources and cleanse the data to match the platform's requirement.

Identifying possible feature upgrades and optimizations based on client interactions and personal hands-on experience while working with client teams and soliciting feedback.

On the feet problem identification and resolving w.r.t internal and external issues in the system

Learning and understanding investments management and accounting.

Learning different types of investment structures (custodians, banks, etc.) and the type of transactional feed coming from these. Identify how the platform can be improved to match the feeds.

Southside Services LLP Account Associate August 2018 - October 2019 (1 year 3 months) Mumbai-Andheri

Performing Bank reconciliation, Accounting and posting of credit card Receipts.

Verification of check details with Bank of America for daily Insurance AR Generating plans details through Microsoft (Power BI).

Completing day to day assigned tasks, including, reports (CRJ & AR), cash and position break resolution & daily supporting activity.

Bi-weekly reconciliation of sales and credit card receivables.

Daily & Month-end cash & positions reconciliations- as an associate, responsible for reconciling all positions & cash balances across various insurance companies with the statements and report exceptions. While performing reconciliation check the insurance specific plan.

Preparation of MIS in consultation with line manager, recording and categorizing the payments received accordingly in the Accounting Software with predetermined plans.

Posting of Durable Medical Equipment's (DME) Batches for recording of transaction details in Complete Patient Record (CPR) and Rx-30 Peachtree accounting Software

Generation of Cash Receipt Journal (CRJ) on weekly basis for the detailed analysis of the cash received in respective period and give payer wise bifurcated details.

Hands on experience in accounting with Peachtree (customizable accounting software). # Follow up on receivables details with insurance AR team members.

Education

Savitribai Phule Pune University

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Finance \cdot (August 2019 - October 2021)

University of Mumbai

M.Com, Accounting and Finance · (2016 - 2018)

ST' G.G COLLEGE

Bachelor of Commerce, Accounting and Finance · (2013 - 2016)